Guide to the Dwight W. Edwards Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Personal Items and Memorabilia, 1918-1982, n.d.; Series VI
  - "Mission in China of Dwight Woodbridge and Mary Vanderslice Edwards" - manuscript by Robert Brank Fulton, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 211)
  - Biographical documentation, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 212)
  - Travel documents, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 213)
  - Travel documents, 1939-1945 (Box 19, Folder 214)
  - Travel documents, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 215)
  - Photographs, ca. 1963, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 216)